{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Stump Removal \u0026 Grinding Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40328/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40328,"taskName":"Tree Stump - Remove","taskDescription":"Remove a Tree Stump","xmTaskDescriptor":"Stump Removal \u0026 Grinding Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":351,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Tree Stump roots removal trees","textMessagingName":"Remove Tree Stump","rolloverLongDesc":"Complete removal usually requires a backhoe. More commonly a trailer-mounted stump grinding machine is used to grind it down to or below ground-level.","rolloverShortDesc":"Usually involves a commercial stump grinder.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Remove a Tree Stump.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Tree Stump Removal \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Stump Grinding","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":79,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Tree Stump Removal","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Tree Stump - Remove","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Tree Stump Removal Project","urlName":"Tree-Stump-Remove","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Stump Removal \u0026 Grinding Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Tree,Stump,roots,chop","emcCategoryOid":-12074,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":625,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40328/":{"taskOID":40328,"originalTaskOID":40328,"setID":625,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7181,"questionDisplayText":"# of stumps to be removed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many tree stumps need to be removed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11217,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-3","answerDisplayText":"2-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11218,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4-5","answerDisplayText":"4-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11219,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5","answerDisplayText":"More than 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":529,"questionDisplayText":"Location of tree stump","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the tree stump located?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5591,"questionDisplayText":"Wood Chips","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What shall the service professionals do with the wood chips?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3526,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leave as is","answerDisplayText":"Leave as is","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5026,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Rake into a pile","answerDisplayText":"Rake into a pile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2934,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Haul extra away","answerDisplayText":"Haul extra away","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7181,"questionDisplayText":"# of stumps to be removed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many tree stumps need to be removed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11217,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-3","answerDisplayText":"2-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11218,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4-5","answerDisplayText":"4-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11219,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5","answerDisplayText":"More than 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11217,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-3","answerDisplayText":"2-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11218,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"4-5","answerDisplayText":"4-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11219,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5","answerDisplayText":"More than 5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":529,"questionDisplayText":"Location of tree stump","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the tree stump located?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5591,"questionDisplayText":"Wood Chips","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What shall the service professionals do with the wood chips?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3526,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leave as is","answerDisplayText":"Leave as is","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5026,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Rake into a pile","answerDisplayText":"Rake into a pile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2934,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Haul extra away","answerDisplayText":"Haul extra away","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3526,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leave as is","answerDisplayText":"Leave as is","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5026,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Rake into a pile","answerDisplayText":"Rake into a pile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2934,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Haul extra away","answerDisplayText":"Haul extra away","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}